

MONDHER JANDOUBI



+49 17645987298



mondher.jendoubi.98@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/mondher-jandoubi-736928239/

About me

My name is Mondher Jandoubi, and I'm a 25-year-old recent graduate from the University of Braunschweig, where I earned my Bachelor's degree. I have a strong interest and passion for technology, with a focus on both front-end and backend development. Additionally, I'm enthusiastic about exploring the exciting field of machine learning

SKILLS

- Vue
- HTML
- JavaScript
- Java
- React

LANGUAGES

- · English: Professional proficiency
- German: Professional working knowledge
- French: Professional working knowledge
- Arabic: Native level

EXPERIENCE

Bundesdruckerei-Gruppe Dec 2022 - Sept 2023 Working Student

- Entwickelte und pflegte UI/UX-Webkomponenten unter Verwendung von Stencil, einem innovativen Tool zur Erstellung wiederverwendbarer Webkomponenten.
- Nutzte die Frameworks React, Vue und Angular, um interaktive und benutzerfreundliche Webkomponenten zu gestalten und umzusetzen.

Wunschlachen Nov 2023 - Present

Fullstack Developer

- Create intuitive UIs and responsive Vue apps for dental practice management, covering patient records, appointments, billing, and treatment plans.
- Managed backend databases using Directus, ensuring robust data management and efficiency.
- Developed and optimized workflows to enhance operational efficiency in Vue applications.

EDUCATION

Technische Universität Braunschweig Bachelor, Informatik

October 2019 - Sept 2023

 Led a final project in the field of machine learning and natural language processing (NLP), exploring advanced techniques for analyzing and processing natural language data to enhance information extraction and understanding.